

- **6** 0965-718-8624
- marbenvillaflor4@gmail.com
- Zone 10 Bulua, Cagayan de Oro City

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## JUNIOR MOBILE DEVELOPER

Eihap company - (February, 2022 – July, 2022)

- Good collaboration with senior developer.
- Weekly meeting with the CEO
- Task management and continuous progress

### FREELANCE

Small projects - (November, 2021 – Present)

- Good negotiation with clients
- Learning while working on the projects
- Being negotiable to the clients

# ON JOB TRAINING

Emberspec Media Solutions Inc. - (March, 2022 – May, 2022)

- Good time management and task accomplishments.
- Software testing and documentation.
- Attending meeting with the client

# **PROJECTS**

- Eihap app, project(March 2022 -present)
- POS Inventory
- Portfolio
- · Bird collections
- To do list app

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Flutter
- Dart
- Dan
- Java
- JavaScript
- Html
- Laravel
- WordPress
- Git Hub
- Monday Project
  Management tool
- Gimp
- VS code
- Firebase
- Xampp MySQL

# MARBEN C. VILLAFLOR

# Developer

### **PROFILE**

Motivated person in software development who is willing to learn more in the field. Gathering more experience to learn how to work effectively and become more productive. Learning in a workplace to attain more confidence in the work-field is good for quality and productivity.

# **ABOUT MY SELF**

I am a Bachelor of Science and Information Technology (BSIT) upcoming graduate who is motivated and hardworking in software development. Despite of being not excellent and slow learner student I used to do my best of what I can do at every activity I faced. I like also to collaborate with others in terms tasks and projects. I Like to keep forward slowly day by day until I became confident at any part of any field of my career.

### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

University of Science and Information Technology of

Southern Philippines 2018 - Present

**Senior High School** 

Liceo de Cagayan University 2016 - 2018

**Junior High School** 

Bulua National High School 2012 - 2016

**Elementary** 

Bulua Central School 2006 - 2012

### **REFERENCE**

Name: Clark Justine Ty

Email: clark@emberspec.com

**Relationship:** Clark is the CEO of the company and who manages us during my internship for 3 months.



https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100007629078757



https://github.com/MarVills



https://www.linkedin.com/in/marben-villaflor-196613241/